哦,瑞典。
Uh, Sweden.
我…我…瑞典语，但我会说一点英语。
I'm... I'm... Swedish but I speak a little English.
我们要上船了。
We're coming on board.
大家都欢迎。大家都欢迎。
All are welcome. All are welcome.
即使是小的。他也可以来。
Even the little one. He can come too.
受欢迎的。
Welcome.
你为什么在这里?
Why are you here?
只是一个小小的航海假期。
Just a little sailing holiday.
一个快乐的男孩之旅。
A jolly boys trip.
把手拿开。
Take your hands off.
论文?
Papers?
护照吗?
Passport?
给你。
Here you go.
船上还有其他人吗?
Any other people on the boat?
就我们两个。
Just the two of us.
不行。
Nein.
来吧，来吧，我们有很多吃的……把你的脏手拿开!
Come, come, we have lots to eat... Take your dirty hands off me!
后退!
Back off!
还有你，把手举起来!
And you, put your hands in the air!
噢!
Ooh!
你现在有麻烦了!
You're in trouble now!
你真是个淘气的孩子!
You've been a naughty boy!
我给你100法郎，让你杀了他。
I'll give you 100 francs to shoot him.
别开枪打我!
Don't shoot me!
他讨厌德国人。你真该杀了他。
He hates Germans. You should really shoot him.
我…我很抱歉。你太吓人了。
I... I'm sorry. You are very scary.
让他走跳板。
Make him walk the plank.
他喜欢木头。
He loves wood.
肮脏的醉鬼!
Dirty drunken animal!
罪名成立。
Guilty as charged.
我总是带一罐煤油来应付这种情况。
I always take a can of kerosene for just these sort of occasions.
已经有一段时间了，但上次我登船时有人嘲笑我，我给了他们选择的机会。
It's been a while, but the last time someone laughed at me when I boarded their vessel, I gave them the choice.
要么游到岸边，要么在燃烧的船上碰碰运气。
Either swim to shore or take their chances on a burning ship.
汉斯和我不知道他们会选择哪一个，是被水淹死还是被火烧死。
Hans and I wondered which option they'd choose, death by water or death by fire.
奇怪的是，他们两者都选了。
Oddly, they chose both.
他们一直等到最后一刻，等到头发都烧起来了，手指上的水泡都剥落了，才跳进水里，幻想着能上岸。
They waited until the very last moment, until their hair was on fire, and their blistered skin peeled from their fingers, before they immersed themselves in water in the vain hope of reaching shore.
其中一艘立刻沉没了。
One of them sank immediately and perished.
但令我们惊讶的是，那个大个子，他表现出了伟大的精神。
But to our amazement, the big one, he showed great spirit.
尽管所有的可能性... ...他费力地游到岸边。
In spite of all the odds... ... he painstakingly made it to shore.
我们跟着他，为他欢呼，并向他的后脑勺开了一枪来奖励他这一令人印象深刻的成就。
We followed and cheered him on and rewarded this impressive achievement with a bullet to the back of his head.
这不是很有趣吗?
Isn't that funny?
你为什么不笑?
Why aren't you laughing?
干得好，拉森。
Nice work, Lassen.
还有更多的来源。
There's more where that came from.
是的。
Yes.
啊…我不确定它是否有效，拉森。
Ah... Not sure it's working, Lassen.
船长看起来相当不安。
The captain looks rather agitated.
他们带着枪来了。
They're bringing their guns to bear.
他们很快就会找到射程的，长官。
They'll find their range soon, sir.
弗雷迪，我们该担心吗?
Freddy, should we be worried?
哦，我不这么认为，先生。
Oh, I don't think so, sir.
这是一个相当大的炸药，所以我放了一个相当大的引信。
It's a rather large explosive, so I set a rather large fuse.
我定位了化妆室的外面，所以当它爆炸的时候，它真的应该爆炸。
I located the outside of the powder room, so when it goes bang, it really should go bang.
靠近……应该马上就到了，伙计们。
Closer... Should be any second now, chaps.
弗雷迪?
Freddy?
干得好，弗雷德里克。
Good work, Frederick.
谢谢你，上尉。
Thank you, Captain.
现在，你能告诉我们在这里做什么吗，先生?
Now, any chance you can tell us what we're doing here, sir?
当希特勒和他的纳粹大军横扫他们前进的道路时，欧洲的战争仍在肆虐。
The war in Europe rages on as Hitler and his Nazi horde sweep aside all in their path.
波兰、比利时和现在的法国都落入了希特勒的法西斯政权之手，让英国背负着整个欧洲解放的最后希望。
Poland, Belgium and now France have all fallen to Hitler's fascist regime, leaving Britain holding up the final hopes of liberation for all of Europe.
来吧，布莱蒂，准备打架吧。
So, come on, Blighty, get ready for a fighty.
但我们不能单独行动。
But we cannot do it alone.
我们的美国兄弟从大西洋彼岸加入我们的任何希望都被德国的秘密武器u型潜艇所挫败。
And any hope for our American brothers to join us from across the Atlantic remains frustrated by Germany's secret weapon, the U-boat.
这些致命的小潜艇在北大西洋随意捕猎。
These deadly little submarines hunt at will in the North Atlantic.
u型潜艇在无人察觉的情况下，不分青红皂白地击沉了船只，无论是运载弹药、粮食还是从我们的同伴那里驶往大洋彼岸的平民。
Undetectable, the U-boat sinks ships indiscriminately, whether carrying munitions, provisions or civilians heading from our companions across the pond.
只要潜艇还统治着大西洋，美国勇敢的军队就不可能到达我们的海岸。
So long as the U-boats rule the Atlantic, it remains impossible for America's brave troops to reach our shores.
英国是被迫满足希特勒的计划，还是面临希特勒进攻的毁灭?
Will Britain be forced to appease Hitler's plans or face devastation from his offensive?
伦敦被烧得一片通红，上面的炸弹和下面的鱼雷将英国人碾碎。
London burns and her seas run red, as bombs from above and torpedoes from below grind the Brits down.
由于无法防御这些致命的u型潜艇，欧洲和平的希望似乎已荡然无存。
And with no defense against these lethal U-boats, it appears all hope may be lost for peace in Europe.
德国人用u型潜艇切断了我们的供应链，我们也切断了u型潜艇的供应链。
The Germans cut off our supply chain with U-boats, we cut off the supply chain to the U-boats.
通过我们的情报人员，我们找到了办法。
Through our intelligence agents, we've found a way.
希特勒的大西洋潜艇舰队的整个维修、修理和重新武装…由两艘纳粹拖船操纵还有一艘意大利补给船在费尔南多港。
The entire servicing, repairing, and rearming of Hitler's Atlantic U-boat fleet... is operated by two Nazi tug boats... and an Italian supply ship in Fernando Po.
我需要愿意去击沉那些船的人。
I need men who are willing to go and sink those ships.
为什么我们不空袭费尔南多波，把船炸沉呢?
Why don't we just air-raid Fernando Po and sink the ships?
因为狡猾的德国人，狡猾的德国人，把自己定位在西班牙殖民地。
Because crafty Germans, being crafty Germans, have positioned themselves in a Spanish colony.
费尔南多波是中立领土。
Fernando Po is neutral territory.
如果我们进攻那个殖民地，其他未被占领的欧洲国家就会加入纳粹，我们迟早会发现自己只穿着皮短裤煎着粉红色的大香肠。
If we attack that colony, the rest of unoccupied Europe will join the Nazis, and it's only a question of time before we find ourselves frying big pink sausages wearing nothing but lederhosen.
希特勒不按规则办事，我们也一样。
Hitler is not playing by the rules and neither are we.
这当然是一次未经批准，未经授权的非官方行动。
This will of course be an unsanctioned, unauthorized and unofficial mission.
如果他们被英国人抓住，就会被关进监狱。
If they're captured by the British, they'll be thrown in jail.
但如果纳粹找到他们…
But if the Nazis find them...
这是折磨和死亡。
it's torture and death.
也许我找到了合适的人选，但很不方便的是，他现在被陛下下令监禁。
Somewhat contentiously, I may have just the man, but rather inconveniently, he's currently incarcerated at His Majesty's pleasure.
我们也许不喜欢他的态度，但他很大胆，是个杀手，
We may not like his attitude, but he's bold, he's a killer,
他们会跟着他去任何地方。
and the men will follow him anywhere.
你确定这是个好主意吗?
Are we sure this is a good idea?
当然不是。
Of course we're not.
但我们走投无路了。
But we're desperate.
-让他进来。
- Send him in.
前进!
Forward!
站在那儿，少校。
Stand there, Major.
谢谢你，中士。
Thank you, Sergeant.
格斯·马奇·菲利普斯，我是中校…弗莱明。伊恩·弗莱明。
Gus March-Phillips, this is Lieutenant Commander... Fleming. Ian Fleming.
他以前在海军情报局工作，现在为我工作。
He used to be at Naval Intelligence, now he works for me.
我为什么在这里，先生?
Why am I here, M?
我有个任务想让你负责。
I have a mission I want you to lead.
你为什么问我，先生?
Why are you asking me, M?
喝杯茶吧，少校。
Help yourself to a cup of tea, Major.
我们都知道我…
We both know that I'm...
不太受政府欢迎。
not very popular with the administration.
他们觉得你没有吸引力的原因正是我觉得你有吸引力的原因。
The reason they find you unattractive is the very reason I find you attractive.
使命?
Mission?
操作邮政局长。
Operation Postmaster.
在北大西洋压制德国的u型潜艇。
To neutralize the German U-boats in the North Atlantic.
-你有什么计划?
- And, uh, what's the plan?
潜艇需要燃料和鱼雷。——哦。
The U-boats need - fuel and torpedoes. - Oh.
但它们也需要二氧化碳过滤器来过滤氧气。
But they also need carbon dioxide filters for oxygen.
没有它们，它们就不能潜水，也不能捕猎。
Without them, they can't dive and they can't hunt.
停留在表面上，它们已经过时了。
Stuck on the surface, they're obsolete.
目标?
Target?
奥斯塔公爵夫人。
The Duchessa d'Aosta.
她是一艘意大利船，德国人一直在用……
She's an Italian ship the Germans have been using...
…为整个舰队加油，重新武装并补充二氧化碳过滤器。
...to refuel, re-arm and replenish the CO2 filters for the entire fleet.
她藏在西非海岸。
She's hidden off the coast of West Africa.
一个叫费尔南多岛的小岛。
A small island called Fernando Po.
我们想让你把她沉下去。
We want you to, um, sink her.
你们要假扮渔民乘坐一艘拖网渔船沿着西海岸航行船上的炸药足以摧毁公爵夫人号。
You'll be posing as fishermen sailing down the west coast on board a trawler loaded with enough explosives to destroy the Duchessa.
这是赫伦探员和斯图尔特探员。
This is Agents Heron and Stewart.
他们会在岛上做卧底。
They'll be working undercover on the island.
赫伦先生已经在那里站稳了脚跟，经营着各种业务。
Mr. Heron's already established there, running various businesses.
什么业务?
What businesses?
赌场酒吧，非法出口游戏。
A casino bar, and illegal exports game.
盈利?
Profitable?
-我做得很好。
- I do quite well.
高级纳粹分子是我最有价值的客户。
High-ranking Nazis are my most valued clients.
对你有好处。
Good for you.
斯图尔特小姐是一名演员兼歌手，在过去的两年里一直和我们一起训练。
Miss Stewart, an actress and singer, has been training with us for the last two years.
她会假扮成纽约来的黄金交易员。
She'll be posing as a gold trader from New York.
她的任务是引诱并分散岛上指挥官海因里希·鲁尔的注意力。
Her mission is to seduce and distract the island's Commanding Officer Heinrich Luhr.
她很能干，而且有点上进心。
She's very capable and somewhat motivated.
动机是什么，先生?
Motivated how, sir?
我母亲是德国犹太人。
My mother's side were German Jews.
他们是第一个走的。
They were the first to go.
很抱歉听到这个消息。
Very sorry to hear that.
我相信你会康复的。
I'm sure you'll recover.
离纳粹转移行动还有44天。
We have 44 days before the Nazis move their operation.
我们再也找不到他们了。
We won't find them again.
如果我要这么做，我需要我自己的团队。
If I'm to do this, I'll need my own team.
你不会喜欢他们的。他们都…
You won't like them. They're all, uh...
疯了。
mad.
他们需要这样做。告诉我们他们的名字。
They'll need to be. Give us their names.
亨利·海耶斯。
Henry Hayes.
一个聪明的年轻爱尔兰人，他讨厌纳粹，因为他的哥哥，我的好朋友，在一艘u型潜艇击沉了他的拖网渔船后淹死了。
A smart, young Irishman who hates the Nazis because his older brother, who was a close friend of mine, drowned after a U-boat sank his fishing trawler.
从那以后，我一直把他置于我的庇护之下。
I've taken him under my wing ever since.
他狡猾、安静、老谋深算。
He's cunning, quiet and wily.
更重要的是，海耶斯是个出色的水手，我信任他。
More to the point, Hayes is a magnificent sailor and I trust him.
如果我们想弄沉一艘大船，我们需要"巴斯"蛙人弗雷迪。
If we're going to try and sink a large ship, we'll need Freddy "The Buzz" frogman.
他可以把双脚绑在一起游过海峡。
He can swim across the channel with his feet tied together.
无可否认，他是个纵火犯除非他在破坏什么东西，否则他就是个悲惨的人。
Admittedly, he's a convicted arsonist and a terrible misery unless he's destroying something.
但他很擅长炸东西。
But he's very good at blowing things up.
接下来，我们需要丹麦锤。
Next, we'll need the Danish hammer.
安德斯·拉森。
Anders Lassen.
从小就在他家的庄园里和熊搏斗，打麋鹿。
Grew up wrestling bears and hunting elk on his family estate.
他是拿着鲍伊刀和弓箭的传奇人物。
He's a legend with a Bowie knife and a bow and arrow.
在盖世太保将他的兄弟折磨致死后，他在18岁时离家出走，与纳粹作战。
He ran away at 18 to fight the Nazis after the Gestapo tortured his brother to death.
他放弃了切鱼片的游戏，转而开膛破肚。
He gave up filleting game for gutting Nazis.
然后他出现在我们的海岸，准备与我们并肩作战。
He then turned up on our shores ready to fight alongside us.
他是一条无法控制的疯狗，知道一百种创造性的杀人方法。
He is an uncontrollable mad dog who knows a hundred creative ways to kill a man.
最后，也是最重要的，我们需要杰弗里·阿普尔亚德。
And finally, and most importantly, we'll need Geoffrey Appleyard.
是的，我们就知道你会。
Yes, we thought you might.
所以我们派他去费尔南多·波进行侦察任务。
That's why we sent him on a reconnaissance mission to Fernando Po.
不幸的是，他一回来就被纳粹抓走了。
Unfortunately, the Nazis nabbed him on his return.
那就更有理由了。他知道我们需要知道的。
All the more reason. He knows what we need to know.
他是规划大师，幸存者大师，国际象棋大师和刀锋外科医生。
He's a master planner, a master survivor, a chess grand master and a surgeon with the blade.
我们在敦刻尔克的散兵坑里呆了两周，如果不是因为苹果，我今天可能还在那里。
We spent two weeks together in a Dunkirk foxhole and if it wasn't for Apple, I would still be there today.
没有苹果，就没有使命。
No Apple, no mission.
恐怕这是不可能的。
I'm afraid that's impossible.
为什么?
Why?
因为他被拉帕尔马岛上的整个德国驻军关押着。
Because he's being held by an entire German garrison on La Palma.
拉帕尔马已经在路上了。
La Palma's on the way.
-这太疯狂了。-让我来操心吧。
- That's insanity. - You let me worry about that.
我必须给自己买一件那种外套。
I must get me one of those coats.
现在，你能告诉我们在这里做什么吗，先生?
Now, any chance you can tell us what we're doing here, sir?
把自己擦干，蛙人，我来告诉你。
Dry yourself off, frogman, and I'll tell you.
我们都被好奇心吞噬了，先生。
The curiosity is eating us all up, sir.
我为我的秘密道歉，伙计们。
I apologize for all the secrecy, chaps.
但这是一个未经批准的，非官方的，未经授权的任务。
But this is an unsanctioned, unofficial and unauthorized mission.
如果我们被英国人抓了，我们都会进监狱的。
If we're picked up by the Brits, we will all go to jail.
如果我们被德国人抓到，就会被折磨致死。
If we're picked up by the Germans, torture and death.
那就我们四个人了吗?
So, it's just the four of us then?
还有阿普尔亚德船长。
And Captain Appleyard.
他负责确保这些信息的安全。
He's responsible for securing this information.
然而，他遇到了一点麻烦。
He is, however, in a spot of bother.
他被德国人关押在拉帕尔马岛。
He is being held by the Germans on La Palma.
我们的首要任务是解救他。
Our first job is to liberate him.
-哦，就这些了，是吗?-不。
- Oh, so, that's all, is it? -No.
我们需要确认阿普尔亚德的情报。
We need to confirm Appleyard's intelligence.
所以我们说话的时候，还有两名探员正坐火车去费尔南多·波。
That's why there are two more agents on their way to Fernando Po by train, as we speak.
到底在做什么?
Doing what, exactly?
他们会确保那些飞船装满补给，所以一开始就值得炸掉。
They'll be ensuring that those ships are filled with supplies, so they're worth blowing up in the first place.
占领世界是一回事，但他们也必须占领厨房吗?
It's one thing taking over the world, but do they have to take over the kitchen too?
全是香肠，卷心菜和黑面包。
It's all sausage, cabbage and black bread.
你更喜欢谁?
Who would you have preferred?
法国人提供精致的古典风格。
The French offer the refined classical take.
Cote de boeuf, fromage, le beurre…-够了!
Cote de boeuf, fromage, le beurre... - ca suffit!
那意大利人那种质朴的自发性呢?
What about the rustic spontaneity of the Italians?
他们的油，扁面条，西红柿。
Their oils, the linguine, the tomatoes.
我会爬过扁面去拿意大利细面条。
I'd climb over the linguine to get to the fettucine.
但是青鸟。
But the cinghiale.
嗯。
Mmm.
你让我和野猪在一起。
You have me with the wild boar.
不过话又说回来，西班牙人也提供当地的海鲜饭和西班牙餐前小吃。
But then again, the Spanish offer the smorgasbord of the regional paella and tapas.
还有安达卢西亚的伊比利亚。
And Jamon Iberico Andalucia.
所以呢?
So?
我们正处于进退两难的境地。
We're between a rock and a hard place.
如果英国人赢了战争，我们就只能吃炸鱼薯条了。
If the Brits win the war, we're stuck with fish and chips.
如果德国人赢了战争，我们就只能吃这个菜单了。
If the Germans win the war, we're stuck with this menu.
所以呢?
So?
我们要香肠、卷心菜和黑面包。
We'll have the sausage, the cabbage - and the black bread please.
很好。谢谢。
Tres bien. Merci.
我们的情况吗?
Our situation?
稳定。
Steady.
现在。
Now.
嗯。
Mmm.
我累坏了。
I'm exhausted.
对不起,请。
Entschuldigung, bitte.
停止!
Halt!
有什么问题吗?
Is there a problem?
我自己能行，谢谢。
I can manage myself, thank you.
请允许我，斯图尔特小姐。
Allow me, Miss Stewart.
请允许我。
Allow me.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
祝健康!
Prost!
门。
Door.
锁着的。
Locked.
案例?
Case?
正在努力。
Working on it.
先生,联系。
Sir, contact.
——接触。
- Contact.
站在。
Standing by.
Duchessa的清单。准备好了吗?
Duchessa's manifest. Ready?
——准备好了。- 400枚b级鱼雷检查。
- Ready. - 400 B-grade torpedoes. Check.
400枚b级鱼雷。
400 B-grade torpedoes.
检查。
Check.
5000吨柴油。检查。
5,000 tons of diesel. Check.
5000吨柴油。
5,000 tons of diesel.
——中尉。是的,先生?
- Lieutenant. -Yes, sir?
检查。
Check.
—。
-Check.
一万个二氧化碳过滤器。检查。
10,000 carbon dioxide filters. Check.
鹳鸟的消息结束了，长官。
End of message from Stork, sir.
确认收据。
Confirm receipt.
收到确认。
Receipt confirmed.
紧急,首相别墅。
Urgent, Chequers.
把车准备好。通知弗莱明。
Get the car ready. Inform Fleming.
我们收拾行李吧。
Let's pack it up.
如果金库里没有黄金，抢劫银行就没有意义了。
No point robbing the bank if there's no gold in the vault.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
知道世界上至少还有一位绅士，真是令人欣慰。
It's truly comforting to know there's at least one gentleman in the world.
啊!白痴!
Ah! Idiot!
美好的一天。
Good day.
香肠、卷心菜和黑面包。
Sausage, cabbage and black bread.
希特勒给了我们一个提议。
Hitler has made us an offer.
一个绥靖政策。
An appeasement.
但我们必须让我们的陆军下台，交出我们的海军，接受纳粹的统治。
But we must step down our army, surrender our Navy and accept Nazi rule.
否则，他承诺彻底摧毁不列颠及其帝国。
Otherwise, he promises total destruction of Britain and her empire.
我们最好的选择就是趁我们还能接受希特勒的交易。
Our best option is to take Hitler's deal while we can.
空军元帅表示同意。
The Air Marshal agrees.
他有更多的炸弹，更多的人，更多的机器。
He has more bombs, more men, more machines.
我们活不了多久了。
We won't survive much longer.
你必须做出你唯一能凭良心做出的决定，首相。
You have to make the only decision you can make in good conscience, Prime Minister.
天啊，姑娘们。听听你们自己的声音。
Good God, girls. Listen to yourselves.
这不是绥靖，这是投降。
It's not appeasement, it's surrender.
你还是没意识到我们面对的是谁。
You still fail to realize who we're up against.
恕我直言，首相，是你没意识到。
With respect, Prime Minister, it's you who doesn't realize.
我们不能指望打败他。
We cannot hope to defeat him.
希特勒是邪恶的主要来源，是一个穷光蛋。
Hitler is the mainspring of evil, a guttersnipe.
这不是一个我们可以讨价还价的人。
This is not a man that we can negotiate with.
我读过他的书，庞德上将。
I've read his book, Admiral Pound.
这个人是个恶毒的、受害的空想家。
The man is a vicious, victimized ideologue.
他不可信。
He cannot be trusted.
如果我认为我们可以通过投降来实现和平，我早就投降了。
If I thought that we could've achieved peace through surrendering, I'd have done it already.
我们需要让我们的国家不再挨饿。
We need to stop our country from starving.
我们每个月需要三百万吨物资才能横渡大西洋。
We need three million tons of supplies to cross the Atlantic every month.
我们现在损失了一半的潜艇攻击。
We are currently losing 50% of that to U-boat attacks.
另一个接受交易的理由。
Another reason to take the deal.
我还没说完，阿尔杰农，亲爱的。
I've not finished, Algernon, darling.
我们需要美国人，如果我们已经是失败的一方，他们永远不会参战。
We need the Americans, and they will never enter the war if we already appear to be a losing side.
结束与德国的敌对状态是摆脱这场混乱的最佳途径。
Ending hostilities with Germany is the best path out of this mess.
我们都同意，首相。
We are all in agreement, Prime Minister.
谢谢你们，先生们。
Thank you, gentlemen.
是的，谢谢你们，先生们!
Yes, thank you, gentlemen!
弗莱明，这最好是个好消息。
M, Fleming, this better be good news.
首相，这是旅客清单，先生。
Prime Minister, we have the manifest here, sir.
已经证实公爵夫人号满载补给可以保证u型潜艇无限期作战。
It's been confirmed the Duchessa is fully laden with supplies to keep the U-boats operational indefinitely.
如果我们要击沉她，现在是时候了。
If we're going to sink her, now is the time.
他们在路上了。
They're on their way.
他们的机会呢?
And their chances?
如果有人能，那就是他们。
Well, if anyone can, they can.
但如果我们被发现，议会会罢免你。
But if we're discovered, parliament will remove you from office.
那我们最好确保不被人发现。
Well, we'd better make sure we're not discovered then.
我们从悬崖边取下来。
We'll take it from the cliffside.
这是一个85英尺高的陡坡。
It's an 85-foot sheer climb.
没有人会注意到一艘无害的小渔船。
No one should notice a small, innocuous fishing vessel.
我们在树林里埋伏，看看对手是谁，然后进行夜间突袭。
We'll set up in the woods and see what we're up against, then we'll go for a night raid.
悄悄溜进去，找到苹果，迅速出来。
Slip in quietly, find Apple, come out fast.
数字?
Numbers?
情报显示有50到60人的驻军。
Intelligence suggests a garrison of 50 to 60.
每个应该是15个。
That should be about 15 each.
拉森，别贪心。你确实很有名气。
Lassen, try not to be greedy. You do have a reputation.
我杀人的日子结束了。
My killing days are over.
我只是作为维和观察员来的。
I'm just here as a peacekeeping observer.
弗莱迪，装好装备，关掉武器。
Freddy, bag the kit, silence the weapons.
我们什么时候走?
When do we go?
0200.
先占领塔，然后进入无线电室，兵营，最后进入控制室……
Take the towers first, then move onto the radio room, barracks and end up in the control room...
-这是什么?
- What do we have here?
盖世太保。
Gestapo.
你怎么知道的?
How'd you know?
他们越坏，穿得越好。
The badder they are, the better they're dressed.
我真得去买一件那种外套。
I really must get me one of those coats.
他们一定是来找苹果的。
They must be here for Apple.
要么是严刑拷打，要么是撤离，长官。
It's either torture or, uh, extraction, sir.
如果他们把他抓出来，苹果就完蛋了。
If they extract him, it'll be the end of Apple.
我们不会再见到他了。
We won't be seeing him again.
先生们，恐怕我们今晚没那么奢侈了。
I'm afraid, gentlemen, we're not going to have the luxury of night.
我们现在得进去了。
We're going to have to go in now.
那么，那里发生了什么?
So, what's happened there then?
看起来像是被箭填满了，海赛。
It looks like they've been plugged full of arrows, Haysey.
那么，箭头去哪了?
Well, where did the arrows go?
直接穿过它们。
Straight through them.
另一边还有两只。
There were two more round the other side.
他们现在在哪里?
Where are they now?
和这两个一样。
Same place as these two.
纳粹的天堂。
Nazi heaven.
我们还有不到七分钟的时间，他们就会失手。
Well, we've got less than seven minutes before they're missed.
警报,狗。都不好。
Alarms, dogs. None of it good.
去引擎的卧底。
Go undercover of the engine.
只有发生爆炸的时候才会暴露。
Only break cover when things go bang.
我有个好主意，拉森。
I have a great idea, Lassen.
你为什么不自己去把那些德国人的箭射满?
Why don't you march off by yourself and fill those Germans full of arrows?
弗莱迪，拿剪刀帮他修栅栏。
Freddy, grab the scissors and help him with that fence.
啊,先生。
Aye, sir.
海西，你跟我来。我们向左走。
Haysey, you're with me. We go left.
弗雷迪，拉森，你们走右边。
Freddy, Lassen, you go right.
准备好靴子，先生们，祝你们胃口好。
Fill your boots, gentlemen, and bon appetit.
-塔上见。
- See you at the tower.
记住，先生们，要玩得开心。
And remember, gentlemen, try to have fun.
-到目前为止还好。
-  So far, so good.
-做得很好，Haysey。
- Doing rather well, Haysey.
哦，谢谢你，先生。
Oh, why thank you, sir.
非常好。
It's very good.
听起来隐身模式结束了。
Sounds like stealth mode's over.
Haysey,失望!
Haysey, down!
——不行!不行!
- Nein! Nein!
我们认识吗?
Do we know each other?
——没有。
- No.
那是一颗心吗，拉森?
Is that a heart, Lassen?
为免生疑问。
For the avoidance of doubt.
苹果，老伙计。
Apple, old boy.
——格斯。-我看你们俩见过面。
- Gus. -I see you two have met.
这是Haysey。
This is Haysey.
快乐,Haysey。-我也很高兴。
-Pleasure, Haysey. - Pleasure's mine.
我想你可能需要这些。
I thought you might need these.
你想得真周到。
Jolly thoughtful of you.
你们都找到他了吗?
You all find him?
哦,太好了。
Oh, goody.
妈的，你的乳头怎么了?
Bloody hell, what happened to your nipples?
你没事吧?
You all right?
你不能拔掉我的电源，对吧?电池还开着。
Couldn't unplug me, could you? Battery's still on.
你看到公爵夫人号和拖船了吗?
Did you see the Duchessa, the tug boats?
还有很多纳粹士兵。
And rather a lot of Nazi soldiers.
你的报告里怎么没写?
Why wasn't that in your report?
因为那些士兵，那些枪，还有那些s艇都是新的。
Because those soldiers and those guns, and those S-Boats are all new.
这比男孩们期望的要多得多。
That's a lot more than the boys are expecting.
一个月前，只有十几个机械师。
A month ago, it was a dozen mechanics.
六个喝醉的水手。
Six drunk sailors.
两个胖西班牙人。
Two fat Spaniards.
还有一个站在梨树上的纳粹。
And a Nazi in a pear tree.
我得说，我们需要更多的帮助。
I'd say, we're gonna need more help.
这件事交给我吧。
You leave that to me.
-当然。
- Of course.
但现在…-…你得见见那个人。
-But right now... - ...you need to meet that man.
你的男人。你来这里的原因。
Your man. The reason you're here.
啊。
Ah.
唯一比纳粹更坏的…是他。
The only thing worse than a Nazi... is him.
我很失望，苍鹭。
I'm very disappointed, Heron.
在我的仓库里有16个箱子你还没有运到大陆。
There are 16 crates in my warehouse you have not yet shipped to the mainland.
不用担心，鲁尔先生。
No need to fret, Herr Luhr.
他们仍然会在约定的日期交货。
They'll still be delivered by the agreed date.
也许吧。
That may be.
但它们占用了宝贵的空间。
But they take up valuable space.
为此，我希望你的费用能大幅降低。
For this, I expect a significant reduction in your fee.
-我可以做5%... ...作为善意的表示。
-I can do 5%... ... as a gesture of goodwill.
二十。别浪费我宝贵的时间来讨价还价。
Twenty. And don't waste my precious time haggling.
严格来说，不应该减薪，因为还没有任何违约行为。
Well, strictly speaking, there should be no reductions, since there's not yet been any breach of contract.
五听起来很礼貌，二十听起来像个酸音，很刺耳。
Five is more than polite, 20 rings like a sour note, it jars.
罐子吗?
It jars?
我被指责不和谐吗?
Am I being accused of disharmony?
我认为这是对我个人的侮辱。
I take that as a personal affront.
我猜你不是秘书吧。
And I am supposing you are not the secretary.
斯图尔特小姐是我安排的联系人。
Miss Stewart is the contact I said I'd arrange.
你的纽约黄金联系人?
Ah, your New York gold contact?
我告诉过你，我已经有了一个满意的安排。
I told you, I already have a satisfying arrangement.
请坐。
Have a seat.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我希望我不会让你失望。
Well, I hope I don't disappoint.
我不能就这次展示做决定。
I can't make a decision on this presentation.
早期的天。
Early days.
好吧，如果早期的日子来得太快，季节随着猎人的月亮而变化。
Well, if early days do come too soon, and seasons change with a Hunter's Moon.
嗯。
Hmm.
我不得不说，苍鹭，尽管你有那么多缺点，但你确实有从帽子里变兔子的习惯。
I have to say, Heron, for all your flaws, you do have a habit of pulling rabbits from hats.
那么，你想转移多少金子-斯图尔特小姐?
So, how much gold do you wish to move, - Miss Stewart?
你能找到多少就有多少。
As much as you can find.
正如我之前提到的，我已经有了一个非常有利可图的安排。
As I mentioned before, I do already have a very profitable arrangement.
不管你怎么评论，我为自己能保持和谐而自豪。
And despite of your commentary, I pride myself on maintaining harmony.
我为什么要招待你?
Now, why should I entertain you?
因为你会赚更多的钱，同时也会有很多乐趣。
Because you'll make more money and have lots of fun whilst doing so.
如果我不守信，就别给我钱。
If I'm not good for my word, don't pay me.
布拉沃。
Bravo.
我会和我的人谈谈，然后我们会合。
I will talk to my people and then we'll rendezvous.
可爱。
Lovely.
当狡猾的红猫在黎明吠叫，为了自己的快乐而杀人时，谁会分享猫偷来的食物呢?
When the sly red cat barks at dawn, and kills just for her pleasure, who shares the meal the cat did steal when both looked on in pleasure?
再会。
Auf wiedersehen.
这个谜语写得不错。
The riddle was a nice touch.
钩子进去了。
The hook's in.
现在要小心怎么把他钓上来。
Now be careful how you reel him in.
孩子们到的时候，我会确保港口是空的。
I'll make sure the harbor's empty when the boys arrive.
你打算怎么做呢?
How are you going to do that?
我会在我的俱乐部办个派对。
I'll throw a party at my club.
军官们的化装舞会和士兵们在码头举行的第二场晚会。
A costume party for the officers and a second party at the dock for the soldiers.
人们喜欢我的派对。
People like my parties.
除了鲁尔。
Everyone but Luhr.
那将是你的工作。
That will be your job.
所有的老鼠都会跟着风笛手。
All the rats will follow the piper.
如果我没理解错的话，我们现在是在拉帕尔马。
So, if I understand correctly, we're currently here in La Palma.
我们将绕着德国控制的非洲航行到费尔南多波，它就在赤道以北，离西非海岸不远。
We'll sail around German-controlled Africa to Fernando Po, which is just north of the Equator, just off the West African coast.
这是最短的路线吗?
So that's the shortest route?
是的，但我们不想剪短。
Yes, but we don't want to go shorter.
我们的首要任务是不让人看到。
Our priority is not to be seen.
你是说，再被人看见。
You mean, be seen again.
一遍吗?现在对我们有点草率了吗，古西?
Again? Getting a little sloppy on us now, Gussy?
已经发生冲突了吗?
Had a run-in already?
别管我们了，苹果，老伙计。
Never mind us, Apple, old boy.
再提醒我一次你是怎么发现你的乳头粘在汽车电池上的。
Remind me again how you found your nipples attached to a car battery.
是的。不是我的错。
Yes. Wasn't my fault.
坏的情报。另外，看这部电影也是值得的。
Bad intelligence. Plus it was almost worth it to watch the heart-snatcher at work.
与其说我是个斗士，不如说我是个爱人。
I'm better known as a lover than a fighter.
耶稣基督!
Jesus Christ!
如果你就是这样吵架的，我可不想看到你爱。
If that's how you fight, I'd hate to see you love.
你不用担心，我配不上你这么漂亮。
You don't have to worry about that, you're too pretty for me.
弗雷迪，另一方面…你得先抓住我。
Freddy, on the other hand... You'd have to catch me first.
我确实喜欢打猎。
I do love to hunt.
你会很幸运的。
You'd be lucky.
我真的很热。
I'm really getting quite hot.
不管怎样，我的建议是我们走这条更宽的路。
Anyway, my suggestion is that we take this wider route.
它显然更长，但应该避免与德国u型潜艇或英国军舰进行尴尬的对话。
It's obviously longer but it should avoid any awkward conversations with German U-boats or British warships.
视天气而定，我们应该在15天内到达。
Weather-dependent, we should make it there in 15 days.
同意了。
Agreed.
海西，你觉得你能做到吗?
Haysey, do you think you could manage that?
交给我吧，先生。
Leave it to me, sir.
照我说的去做——再给我拿一杯来!
Just do as you're told - and get me another drink!
队长,先生。
Captain, sir.
要我给你拿点吃的吗?
Can I get you something to eat?
我可以……这边走。
May I... Come this way.
-把手拿开。
- Take your hands off me.
你知道吗，我喜欢你，费米。
You know, I like you, Femi.
但你再碰我，你就进监狱。
But you touch me again and you're going to jail.
Femi。
Femi.
我来对付他。
I'll deal with him.
请照顾斯图尔特小姐。
Please take care of Miss Stewart.
你知道你需要什么吗，比尼亚上尉?
You know what you need, Captain Binea?
我知道我需要什么。
I know what I need.
但你呢，里卡多?
But do you, Ricardo?
你需要再喝一杯。
You need another drink.
马蒂，好东西。
Marty, good stuff.
里卡多，所以我才爱你。
Ricardo, that's why I love you.
-你懂的。
- You understand.
我是费尔南多·波。
This is Fernando Po.
每个人的欢迎。
Everybody's welcome.
如果……每一个人。
Si... Everybody.
我觉得人太多了。
Too many body I think.
阿曼德?
Armando?
你和我们的新朋友闹翻了吗?
Have you fallen out with our new friends?
这不公平，里卡多。
It's not fair, Ricardo.
这是我的港湾。
This is my harbor.
我说了算。
I am in charge.
他们踩到你的脚趾了吗?
Are they stepping on your toes?
他们不是踩，而是跺脚!
They don't step, they stamp!
他们什么也没告诉比尼亚船长。
They tell Captain Binea nothing.
现在我才听说公爵夫人要提前离开港口。
Only now do I hear the Duchessa is leaving the harbor early.
好吧，总算摆脱了。
Well, good riddance.
这个港口又将是你的了。
The harbor will be yours again.
你什么时候才能摆脱那艘丑陋的船?
When will you be free of that ugly vessel?
三天前。
Three days earlier.
那我们应该再喝一杯。
Then we should have another drink.
庆祝。马蒂……请我们的港务长再来一杯。
To celebrate. Marty... Another round for our Harbor Master.
上尉，你知道他们想搬到哪里吗?
So, Captain, do you know where they wish to relocate?
既不是猫也不是狗为了好玩而杀人，是雌狐，而不是别的。
It's neither cat nor dog that kills for fun, it's the vixen, not another.
只有两种动物以杀戮为乐，我漂亮的朋友，狐狸和他的人类兄弟。
There's only two that kill for fun, my pretty friend, the fox and his human brother.
我相信我已经解开了你的小谜题。
I believe I have resolved your little riddle.
帽子。你打得很好。
Chapeau. You play well.
说到狐狸，西47街的霍洛维茨和迈耶街。
Speaking of foxes, Horowitz and Meyer, West 47th Street.
你听说过吗?
Have you heard of them?
我想我没有见过。
I don't believe I have, no.
他们是纽约中城最大的黄金交易商你还没听说过吗?
They're the largest gold traders in Midtown New York and you haven't heard of them?
恐怕我没有，没有。
I'm afraid I haven't, no.
当然，我对霍洛维茨和海姆很熟悉。
I am familiar, of course, with Horowitz and Haim.
但是他们在城市的西边。
But they're in the west side of the city.
但话说回来，我相信你已经知道了，不是吗?
But then again, I'm sure you already knew that, didn't you?
我很好奇，你觉得和犹太人打交道怎么样?
I'm curious, how do you find dealing with the Jew?
哦,亲爱的。
Oh, dear.
我从一个陷阱里溜出来，却发现自己又掉进了另一个陷阱。
I've slipped from one snare only to find myself in another.
我该怎么说呢?
How shall I put this?
恐怕你们杰出的领袖误解了古贾胡达部落。
I fear your brilliant leader has mischaracterized the ancient tribe of Jahuda.
他们不仅能在脖子上套着靴子的情况下存活3000年，而且还能在这种情况下繁荣发展……我怀疑这激起了他内心恶魔般的嫉妒。
Their ability to not only survive 3,000 years with a boot on their neck, but to prosper in spite of it... I suspect it inspired satanic jealousy within him.
总之，这位女士似乎抗议得太多了。
In conclusion, it looks as though the lady doth protest too much.
这个亵渎神明的蛋糕上还有樱桃吗，还是你吃完了?
Is there a cherry to go on this blasphemous cake, or have you finished?
我必须承认，我不仅尊敬和钦佩犹太人……
I must confess, not only do I respect and admire the Jew...
我就是其中之一。
I am one.
开玩笑!
Kidding!
他们是贪婪的老鼠。
They're greedy rats.
我想这可能是一段美好友谊的开始。
I think this could be the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
那我就开个派对庆祝一下。
Then I shall throw a party to celebrate.
我不喜欢聚会。
I don't care for parties.
哦,扫兴!每个人都喜欢聚会。
Oh, spoilsport! Everybody loves a party.
公爵夫人比我们预计的提前三天出发。
The Duchessa's leaving three days earlier than we thought.
如果我们不告诉伴娘，他们就来不及了。
If we don't tell the Maid Honor, they'll arrive too late.
传入的。
Incoming.
接触。
Contact.
岛上的杰瑞人比预期的多。
More Jerries on the island than expected.
罐头腌牛肉提前三天从食品储藏室拿出来了。
Tin of corned beef's out of pantry three days early.
我就要这个了。
I'll take that.
这是机密，先生，只有M知道。
It's confidential, sir. For M only.
在提取时，它需要非常…长官，留言，长官。
When it comes to make the extraction, it needs to be a very... Sir. Message, sir.
岛上的杰瑞人比预期的多。
More Jerries on the island than expected.
腌牛肉提前三天从食品储藏室拿出来了。
Corned beef's out of the pantry three days early.
移动得更快。
Move faster.
是的，但这片区域有越来越多的潜艇出没。
Yes, but there's increased U-boat sightings in the area.
先生。
Sir.
任务还在继续。
The mission's still proceeding.
所以岛上有更多的士兵而且船要提前离开?
So, there's more soldiers on the island and the boat's leaving earlier?
是的。
Yes.
那我们怎么才能走得更快呢?
Well, how are we meant to move faster?
我们不能再快了。
We can't move faster.
我们已经尽可能快了。
We're going as fast as we can.
这是一艘渔船，不是快艇。
This is a fishing boat, it's not a speedboat.
首相，公爵夫人12天后就要离开费尔南多堡了。
Prime Minister, the Duchessa's leaving Fernando Po in 12 days.
按照我们目前的时间表，他们会晚到三天。
On our current schedule, they'll arrive three days too late.
还能做到吗?
Can it still be done?
我们还在等菲利普斯少校的回复。
We're still awaiting a response from Major Phillips.
如果我们不能走得快一点，我们就走得短一点。
If we can't move faster, we'll go shorter.
我们可以在12天内到达费尔南多波。
We can get to Fernando Po in 12 days.
等等，你说不能再短了。
Hold on, you said we couldn't go shorter.
不，我是说我们不想剪短。
No, I said we don't want to go shorter.
他说我们会被德国潜艇干掉。
He said we'll get mowed down by a U-boat.
或者更糟，被英国人抓走。
Or worse, picked up by the Brits.
他们的驱逐舰舰队正穿过那里。
Their armada of destroyers are crossing there.
我们真的要在u型潜艇上航行了。
We will literally be sailing over U-boats.
抱歉，伙计们，我们短一点。
Sorry, lads, we go shorter.
Drei, zwei, eins…
Drei, zwei, eins...
先生们，就在我跟你们讲话的时候，伦敦再一次在纳粹的空袭下战栗。
Gentlemen, as I speak to you now, London once again shudders beneath a Nazi onslaught from the skies.
在这样的时刻，人们的心会被唤醒去履行职责。
And at such times, the hearts of men are stirred to duty.
但你们不是这样的人。
But you are not such men.
你被选中不是因为你显赫的荣誉或崇高的理想。
You were not chosen for your conspicuous honor or high ideals.
你被选中是因为你是最后的选择。
You were chosen because you are the last resort.
你被赋予的任务是前所未有的。
The mission you have been given is of a sort never before undertaken.
它需要无情的人，他们会毫不犹豫地屈服于战争公约。
It demands ruthless men, who will not hesitate to stoop beneath the conventions of war.
那些不洗手的人。
Men who do not keep clean hands.
像你这样的男人。
Men like you.
-然而，他们仍然在自己不和谐的和谐中密谋。
- And yet, who still conspire in their own discordant harmony.
他们知道，却不关心，他们可能永远不会回来。
Who know and yet do not care that they may never return.
你们勇往直前，不是为了荣誉，不是为了责任，也不是为了我，而是因为你们是不达目的誓不罢休的人。
And who press onward not for glory, or for duty, or for me, but because you are men who will not stop until it is done.
祝成功,先生们。
Godspeed, gentlemen.
嗯…家伙……那是一艘英国驱逐舰。
Uh... Chaps... That's a British destroyer.
我们该走了。
We should move.
我们跑不掉的，长官。
We can't outrun that, sir.
我们见过他们，他们也见过我们。
Well, we've seen them, they've seen us.
抓紧，荣誉侍女。
Hold fast, Maid Honor.
我们正在准备登船派对。
We're preparing a boarding party.
你好,船长!
Hello, Captain!
没什么令人兴奋的。
Nothing exciting here.
我们只是瑞典渔民。
We're just Swedish fishermen.
往前走，乔根森!
Step forward, Jorgensen!
乔根森，你是瑞典人。
Jorgensen, you're Swedish.
问问他们要去哪里，好吗?
Ask them where they're heading, would you?
不是你，拉森。
Not you, Lassen.
嗯…
Uh...
我想听马奇-菲利普斯试一试。
I want to hear March-Phillips have a go.
啊。
Ah.
很好。
Fair enough.
游戏结束了，指挥官。
Game's up, Commander.
不能责怪一个女孩的努力。
Can't blame a girl for trying.
干得好，少校。
Good effort, Major.
但恐怕你得跟我们一起走了。
But I'm afraid you are going to have to come with us.
请问我们是在谁的授权下被伏击的?
May I ask under whose authority we've been waylaid?
奉庞德将军之命。
On the orders of Admiral Pound.
中尉。
First Lieutenant.
你在国际水域从事未经批准的犯罪活动。
You are pursuing an unsanctioned criminal enterprise in international waters.
你会引起混乱的。
You're going to cause an upset.
我觉得我们有点过气了，指挥官。
I think we're a little past upset, Commander.
史蒂文斯，你有什么发现?
Stevens, what have you got?
我有个提示，先生。
I had a ping, sir.
这个贪婪的小纳粹不会满足于占领大部分欧洲，他要的是我们自己的绿色和宜人的土地。
The greedy little Nazi won't be satisfied with holding most of Europe, he's after our own green and pleasant land.
谢天谢地，你带着你的小木船和五人大军来了。
Well, thank God you're here with your little wooden battleship and your five-man army.
- u艇，方位273。
- U-boat, bearing 273.
—设置告警。
- Sound the alarm.
船上来。
Come aboard.
潜艇靠近。右舷，长官。
U-boat approaching. Starboard side, sir.
战斗站!
Battle stations!
少校，如果你知道什么对你有好处，你就回家吧。-很好，指挥官。
Major, if you know what's good for you, - you'll head home. - Very good, Commander.
海茜，尽快带我们离开鱼雷磁铁。
Haysey, get us away from that torpedo magnet as quickly as possible.
是，长官，苹果，到船尾去。
Aye, sir. Apple, man the stern.
弗雷迪，在主帆上。
Freddy, on the main sail.
拉森到船头去。解开那个站!
Lassen to the bow, now. Untie that station!
看不见你。
Aye.
快点，伙计们!
Quickly now, lads!
帮我们拉起前帆，好吗，孩子们?
Hoist that foresail for us, will you, boys?
主帆准备拉起!
Main sail ready to haul!
好了，弗雷迪，扬起主帆!
All right, Freddy, now raise that main sail!
看不见你。
Aye.
报告听起来。
-Report sounding.
其163年。
-Bearing 163.
拉森，修整主帆，然后系上!
Lassen, trim the main sail and then tie it off!
你怎么能指望好呢?
How do you expect good?
报告听起来。
Report sounding.
轴承115。
Bearing 115.
-发射深水炸弹。
-Fire depth charges.
这就是你的人，能把事情搞定吗?
So, this is your man that gets things done?
他叫坎普·比利……以K开头。
His name is Kamp Billy... with a K.
他上的是英国寄宿学校?
And he went to an English boarding school?
不是普通的寄宿学校。他上的是伊顿寄宿学校。
Not just any boarding school. He went to Eton, the boarding school.
对吧……
Right...
那他在这里做什么?
Then what's he doing here?
他是个王子。
He's a prince.
到底是哪方面的王子?
A prince of what, exactly?
-费尔南多王子!
- The Prince of Fernando Po!
这么说，他既是海盗又是贵族?
So, he's part pirate, part aristocrat?
别致。
Chic.
他也是我们解决方案的一部分。
He's also a part of our solution.
RH。
RH.
KB。
KB.
他回来了。
He's back in town.
首席。
Chief.
好像你总是带着礼物来。
Seems like you always come bearing gifts.
她是给我的吗?
Is she for me?
-祝你好运。
- Good luck with that.
我不适合你，但这些是。
I'm not for you, but these are.
嗯。好东西。美味的。
Mmm. Goodies. Yummy.
-正面…——首席。
-  Ade... - Chief.
加油！加油。
Come on, come on.
有人很有品味。
Someone has taste.
比母鸡的牙齿还稀有。
Rarer than hens' teeth.
好吧，RH告诉我，KB是唯一一个在完成任务时可以交谈的人。
Well, RH tells me that KB is the only man to talk to when it comes to getting things done.
为什么我感觉自己从捕食者变成了猎物?
Why do I feel like I've gone from being - the predator to the prey?
不错的入场，小姐。
Quite an entrance, young lady.
条件是我们要取样……现在。
It's on the condition that we sample them... now.
艾德，摆好桌子。
Ade, set the table.
首席。
Chief.
然后公爵说:“把它推进去，直到它停下来!”
And then the Duke said, "Push it in till it stops!"
你真是个厉害的武器。
You are quite the weapon.
我是对的，我是猎物。
I was right, I was the prey.
我会帮你，因为我不喜欢纳粹。
I'll help you because I don't like Nazis.
不是因为他们是纳粹，而是因为他们是笨蛋。
Not because they're Nazis but because they're gauche.
我会给你一艘船和12个最好的人，包括你的手下。
I'll give you a tug and 12 of my best men, including yours truly.
但如果我帮你，谁来帮我?
But if I'm gonna help you, who's gonna help me?
因为你不是士兵，RH。
Because you're not a soldier, RH.
不，但她是。
No, but she is.
她会射得比你的伴郎还快。
She'll outshoot your best man.
我告诉过你。
I told you.
——不!——不!
- No! - No!
鹳交付。检查。
Stork delivery. Check.
检查。
Check.
二十三岁男孩。检查。
Twenty-three boys. Check.
-送鹤。
- Stork delivery.
二十三岁男孩。
Twenty-three boys.
17岁的女孩。
Seventeen girls.
集合地点在费尔南多堡外20公里处。
Meeting point 20 kilometers outside Fernando Po.
和苍鹭的会合。
The rendezvous with Heron.
你能把我们送到那里吗?
Can you get us there?
如果天气好的话，我可以，先生。
If the weather holds, I can, sir.
我赌20英镑，这事不会有好结果。
Twenty quid says this doesn't end well.
为谁?
For who?
对他们来说。
For them.
你不能把赌注压在自己身上，海赛。这是假球。
You can't bet on yourself, Haysey. That's match-fixing.
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
苍鹭，太久没见了。
Heron, it's been too long.
很高兴见到你，格斯。
Good to see you, Gus.
苹果。
Apple.
这是坎普·比利，费尔南多岛的王子。
This is Kamp Billy, the Prince of Fernando Po.
殿下。
Your Highness.
他同意帮助我们。
He's agreed to help us.
原谅我，但是……我有种奇怪的感觉，好像我们以前见过面。
Forgive me, but... I have a peculiar feeling that we've met before.
我经常听到这样的话。我去过很多地方。
I get that a lot. I'm extremely well-traveled.
不,不。这是一种特殊的感觉。
No, no. It's a particular sense.
我想你不打板球，是吗?
I don't suppose you played cricket, did you?
队长伊顿。21年到22年。
Captained Eton. '21 to '22.
我就知道我认得你的脸!
I knew I knew your face!
就在奖杯柜旁边。
Right next to the trophy cabinet.
一幅八英尺高的巨幅肖像。
An eight-foot-tall huge portrait.
是的，正是这样!
Yes, exactly that!
一只眼睛盯着边界... ...一只眼睛盯着酒吧。
One eye on the boundary... ...one eye on the pub.
很高兴你能上船。
Bloody glad to have you aboard.
真高兴能来，老伙计。
Bloody good to be here, old boy.
这些纳粹分子让人讨厌，我受够了。
I'm very bored with these Nazis making a nuisance of themselves.
我是说，这对生意来说很糟糕。
I mean, it's terrible for business.
我很乐意帮你把他们揍得鼻青脸肿。
I'm only too pleased to help you serve them a bloody nose.
这是一种值得称赞的态度。
That's a commendable attitude.
你的计划是什么?
So, what's your plan?
苹果。
Apple.
我们要击沉公爵夫人号，还有两艘拖船。
We're going to sink the Duchessa, plus the two tugs.
摧毁希特勒在大西洋的u型潜艇舰队
Crippling Hitler's Atlantic fleet of U-boats.
很好。
Very good.
问题是，我们的老朋友纳粹可没这么简单。
The thing is, our old friends the Nazis aren't making it the easiest.
我们寡不敌众。
We're outnumbered two hundred to five.
这里的士兵比我们预计的要多。
There's a few more soldiers than we anticipated.
我觉得我们得再找几个壮汉了。
I think that we're gonna have to find ourselves a few more strapping lads.
正面……
Ade...
对吧……
Right...
是的，我想可以了。
Yes, I think that will do.
我们带了武器，如果你需要的话。
We brought some weapons if you need.
你拿着那些。我们带了我们自己的。
You hold onto those. We brought our own.
Oyah !让他们看看铁器!
Oyah! Show them the iron!
太不可思议了。
Marvelous.
你知道公爵夫人号离港口有200多英尺吧?
You do know the Duchessa is more than 200 feet from the harbor side?
她就在聚光灯下。
And she's in full glare of the lights.
如果不引起不必要的注意，她可不容易沉没。
She's not gonna be easy to sink without attracting unwanted attention.
是的。这就是为什么赫伦会在我们划过去，在船体上装炸药之前，先放一颗炸弹来灭灯。
Yes. That's why Heron will plant a bomb to blow the lights, before we paddle in and rig the hull with explosives.
等炸药引爆，我们就回家了。
By the time the explosives detonate, we'll be heading home.
如果按我的方式来，一枪都不会开。
If I had it my way, a shot'll never be fired.
你多久能按自己的方式来一次?
And how often do you have it your way?
那得看你问谁了，老伙计。
Depends on who you ask, old boy.
先生们……-正面。——首席。
Gentlemen... - Ade. - Chief.
-让人准备好。
- Prepare the men.
你准备好了就给我二十块，弗雷迪。
I'll take that 20 whenever you're ready, Freddy.
公爵夫人明早就会走。
The Duchessa will be gone by the morning.
-你能做到吗?
- Can you manage that?
这是两根电线和一个滴答声。
It's two wires and a tick-tock.
我相信我能应付。
I'm sure I can cope.
你该担心的不是我。
It's not me you should be worried about.
我从来没带纳粹参加过派对。
I've never taken a Nazi to a party.
别去他的派对就行了。
Just don't end up at one of his parties.
别为我担心。
Don't worry about me.
我要办自己的小派对。
I'm gonna have my own little party.
为孩子们干杯，为陛下的政府干杯。
Drink for the boys, on His Majesty's government.
一般来说，我会咬掉你的手，因为大家都知道我很喜欢一英镑纸币。
Ordinarily, I'd bite your hand off, as I have been known to love a pound note.
但这一次，
But on this occasion,
饮料我请。
the drinks are on me.
然而，如果国王陛下的政府颁发头衔……你已经是王子了，老伙计。
However, if His Majesty's government was handing out titles... You're already a prince, old boy.
有费尔南多王子，但是……王国的骑士有一定的古老意义。
There's Prince of Fernando Po, but... a Knight of the Realm has a certain antiquity to it.
起立，坎普·比利爵士。
Arise, Sir Kamp Billy.
你是个好人，格斯。
You're a good man, Gus.
祝你好运，比利。
Good luck, Billy.
你好!
Hola!
好极了，伙计们!
Buenas tardes, companeros!
先生，有客人来了。
My Herr, you have a visitor.
哈!
Ta-da!
克利奥帕特拉需要她的凯撒。
Cleopatra needs her Caesar.
把它穿上。
Put it on.
谢谢你，蒂莫西。
Thank you, Timothy.
1秒。
One second.
盖……我还有个还价。
Timothy... I have a counter offer.
我们把调料放在一边。
Let's put this dressing up aside.
这是给孩子们的。我们不是孩子。
It's for children. And we are not children.
我们自己开派对吧。
Let's make our own party.
一个黑暗的聚会。
A dark party.
黑暗的纳粹党。
A dark Nazi party.
有音乐，润滑剂和帅气的纳粹。
With music, lubrication and a handsome Nazi.
自从我来到这里，我就被吱吱作响的东西咬了，蝎子在我的靴子里筑巢，我无法入睡，因为丛林里无情的嚎叫。
Since I've been here, I've been bitten by things that croak and slither, scorpions nest in my boots and I can't sleep for the relentless howl of jungle entropy.
今晚，我要去那个派对，你带我去。
Tonight, I'm going to that party, and you are taking me.
现在，把它穿上。
Now, put it on.
哦。
Oh.
很好。
Very well.
啊!你好!
Ah! Hola!
灯灭了我们就搬。
We move when the lights go out.
好了，里卡多，今天你是酋长。
All right, Ricardo, today you're El Capitan.
阿曼多，酒吧归你了。
Armando, the bar is yours.
使用它。随意滥用它。
Use it. Abuse it at your will.
这就是为什么我爱你。
That's why I love you.
跟我来，帅哥。
Come with me, handsome.
我要你让他们开心。
I need you to keep the men happy.
如何快乐?
How happy?
嗯。
Mmm.
老鼠在巢里吗?
Are the rats in the nest?
今晚你在其他任何地方都找不到德国、西班牙或意大利军官。
You won't find a German, Spanish or Italian officer anywhere else tonight.
在港口的啤酒节和这个小聚会之间，90%的士兵都离开了码头。
Between the beer fest at the harbor and this little get-together, that'll be 90% of the soldiers away from the dock.
炸弹将在30分钟内炸毁港口灯光。
The charge is set to blow the harbor lights in 30 minutes.
你能把他关那么久吗?
Can you keep him here that long?
傻孩子，傻问题。看看这条裙子。
Silly boy, silly question. Look at the dress.
嗨。
Hi.
你把这叫做派对?
So, you call this a party?
这只是一个开端。
This is just the thin end of the wedge.
我为你准备了一场表演。
I've created a performance just for you.
我可以带你看看真正的派对。
Well, I could show you a real party.
我干嘛在乎，意大利面?
Why do I care, Spaghetti?
披萨。
Pizza.
失陪一下，我去补个粉。
Excuse me while I powder my nose.
-什么，又来了?
- What, again?
别慌，凯撒。温习你的意大利语。
Don't panic, Caesar. Brush up on your Italian.
你的礼物需要包装。
Your gift needs to be wrapped.
请让警官们继续喝酒。
Keep those officers drinking, please.
-当然。好吧。-谢谢你，费米。
- Of course. Okay. - Thank you, Femi.
公爵夫人号的船体已经加固了。
The Duchessa's hull has been reinforced.
它不会沉没。
It won't sink.
我们得停止任务。
We need to stop the mission.
这很难做到。
That's going to be hard to do.
听我说。
Listen to me.
我们的使命将会失败。
Our mission will fail.
炸药不起作用，因为他加固了它，使它永不沉没。
The explosives won't work because he's reinforced it to be unsinkable.
你必须马上阻止他们。
You have to stop them now.
但电荷即将吹灭灯光。
But the charge is about to blow the lights.
如果你不能阻止灯光，那就阻止那些人。
Well, if you can't stop the lights, stop the men.
鲁尔不能离开这个派对。
Luhr must not leave this party.
我会让他忙起来的。去,现在。
I'll keep him busy. Go, now.
我们出发了。
And we're off.
格斯等。
Gus, wait.
鹳鸟呼叫女仆，鹳鸟呼叫女仆，请回答。
Stork to Maid, Stork to Maid, come in.
五频道。
Channel five.
我是梅德。切换到20。
This is Maid. Switching to 20.
去做吧。
Go ahead.
咸牛肉罐头是打不开的。
Tin of corned beef can't be cracked.
船不会被击沉。
The ship cannot be sunk.
炸药会失效。
Explosives will fail.
我是鹳鸟，先生。
It's Stork, sir.
打开扬声器。
Put him on open speaker.
咸牛肉是不能碎的。
Corned beef can't be cracked.
鹳，我是M。
Stork, this is M.
别管咸牛肉了。想办法吧。
Never mind the corned beef. Just find a way.
——结束了。-炸弹来袭，长官。
- Over. - Pound incoming, sir.
重复……-把它关掉。
-Repeat... - Switch that off.
-我们必须…立即停止。
- We must... Stop this immediately.
你们的所作所为到此为止，否则你们每个人都将受到法庭的审判。
What you are doing ends now, or every last one of you will be subject to a tribunal.
明白了吗?
Is that clear?
我不知道你在说什么，先生。
I don't know what you're talking about, sir.
对吗，中士?
Is that correct, Sergeant?
守住阵地。
Hold position.
还有多久，鹳鸟?
How long, Stork?
等待订单。-给我。
-Awaiting orders. - Give me that.
站在。
Stand by.
马奇-菲利普斯，这是庞德上将给你的直接命令。
March-Phillips, this is Admiral Pound giving you a direct order.
立即中止任务。
Abort this mission now.
我保证你们谁也见不到天日。
I will make sure that none of you see the light of day again.
你们的余生都将被关起来听凭陛下的安排。
You will spend the rest of your lives locked up at His Majesty's pleasure.
这包括你们所有人。
That includes all of you.
杰弗里·阿普尔亚德，安德斯·拉森，-弗雷迪·巴斯…-对不起... ...还有亨利·海斯。
Geoffrey Appleyard, Anders Lassen, - Freddy Buzz... -I'm sorry... ...and Henry Hayes.
我不太明白你在说什么。
Can't quite make out - what you're saying.
再见。
Bye.
——是……明白了吗?
- Is... Is that clear?
抱歉?怎么啦？
Sorry? What?
我不能……我听不太清楚。
I can't... I can't quite hear you.
请……滚蛋。
Please... fuck off.
你和你的行动太鲁莽了，准将。
You and your operation are reckless, Brigadier.
我将亲自建议议会罢免首相。
I will personally advise parliament to have the Prime Minister removed from office.
我要让你关门大吉。
And I am going to shut you down.
我明白了，长官。
Message received loud and clear, sir.
我建议你也滚蛋，中士。
I suggest you also fuck off, Sergeant.
弗莱明，联系马奇-菲利普斯。
Fleming, contact March-Phillips.
莉莉，给我接通首相热线。
Lily, get me the Prime Minister on hotline.
-马上，先生-请进，01
-Right away, sir. - Come in, 01.
请进，收到了吗?
Come in, do you receive?
——是吗?-首相，恐怕我们被发现了。
- Yes? -Prime Minister, I'm afraid we've been discovered.
我们中间有内奸庞德上将下令取消这次任务。
There was a mole in our midst and Admiral Pound has ordered the mission to be aborted.
他想让议会罢免你。
He wants to have parliament remove you from office.
这项任务必须继续下去。
The mission must continue.
01，这是底。结束了。
01, this is base. Over.
告诉庞德，如果他有问题，来找我。他知道我住在哪里。
Tell Pound if he has a problem, to take it up with me. He knows where I live.
告诉士兵们继续前进。
Tell the men to press on.
恐怕我们失去了所有的联系，先生。
I'm afraid we've lost all communication, sir.
我们一定能做点什么。
There must be something that we can do.
我唯一能做的就是提醒你，我们选择马奇·菲利普斯的原因是因为他不服从命令。
The only thing I can do is remind you, the reason we chose March-Phillips is because he doesn't follow orders.
希望我们选对了。
Then let's hope we chose well.
公爵夫人号的船体已经加固了。
The Duchessa's hull has been reinforced.
也就是说她不会被击沉。
Which means she can't be sunk.
至少我们带了这么多炸药。
At least not with the amount of explosives we're carrying.
只是想知道这到底是怎么发生的。
Just wondering how and when exactly this took place.
事情发生的时间和方式并不重要。
It's not important how and when, it's happened.
这事挺重要的，格斯。
Well, it is kind of important, Gus.
我不在乎坐牢，但我在乎的是完成我们已经开始的事业。
I don't care about the prison time, but I do care about finishing what we've started.
谢谢你，弗雷迪。
Thank you, Freddy.
一定是搞错了。
There must be some sort of mistake.
你不能只是强化……没有错，Haysey。
You can't just reinforce... There's no mistake, Haysey.
我只是不知道如何以及何时……——够了!
I'm just lost about how and when exactly... - Enough!
我们为什么不把拖船弄沉?
Why don't we sink the tug boats?
把通往潜艇的穿梭机弄掉。
Get rid of the shuttle to the U-boats.
这还不够。
It's not enough.
他们会在一周内换新的。
They'll replace them in a week.
我们为什么不偷呢?
Why don't we steal them?
我们可以用比利的船把公爵夫人号拖出港口然后偷走另外两艘为u型潜艇服务的德国拖船。
We can use Billy's boat to drag the Duchessa out of the harbor and steal the other two German tug boats that service the U-boats.
我们该怎么做呢?
And how are we supposed to do that?
它不仅是双层的，重量是原来的两倍，而且你需要一个完整的船员来移动这么大的船。
Not only is she double-plated, weighing twice as much, but you'd need a full crew to move a ship that size.
拖船是船员。
The tug boats are the crew.
我们把公爵夫人拖到海里，然后，把所有的东西都偷走。
We tow the Duchessa out to the ocean and, well, steal the lot.
然后呢?我们还是不能击沉他们。
Then what? We still can't sink them.
我们不需要。
We don't need to.
我们驶进公海，把一切交给海军。
We sail into international waters and hand everything over to the Navy.
反正他们在跟踪我们，所以他们会很高兴再见到我们的。
They're following us anyway, so they'll be more than happy to see us again.
那主播呢?
And what about the anchor?
你看到它的大小了吗?
Have you seen the size of it?
如果我们真的要转移她，他们的s型船会在几秒内抓住我们。
If we're gonna actually start to move her, their S-boats will catch us in seconds.
你准备怎么处理你带来的炸药，弗雷迪?
Well, what are you going to do with all the explosives you brought, Freddy?
我们要用它们炸掉锚。
We'll use them to blow the anchor.
我们先把s型潜艇装好，这样他们就追不上了，再把供应u型潜艇的燃料储备装好，然后把那里炸了。
We'll rig the S-boats so they can't follow, rig the fuel reserve that supplies the U-boats, and then, well, blow the lot up.
燃料爆炸会把所有人和他们的母亲带到港口。
That fuel explosion's gonna bring everyone and their mother down to the harbor.
我们设置了引信，这样我们一出港口，燃料堆就会爆炸。
We set the fuse, so that the fuel dump blows once we're outside the harbor.
然后我们悄悄溜出去。
Then we sneak out quietly.
不坏。
Not bad.
它非常贪婪。
It's very greedy.
-好吧，我加入。-好吧，除非我有一桶纳粹心脏，否则我是不会走的。
- Well, I'm in. -Well, I'm not leaving until I have a barrel full of Nazi hearts.
我会照你说的做，先生。
I'll do whatever you tell me to do, sir.
先生们,
Gentlemen,
我们去偷几艘船吧。
let's steal some boats.
原来她是双面人，所以计划有变。
Turns out she's double-plated, so change of plans.
我们要去偷船。
We're going to steal the boats instead.
这可能吗?
Is that even possible?
我不太确定。
I'm not entirely sure.
但如果你愿意，我们也一样。
But if you're up for it, so are we.
你知道这意味着什么。
And you know what that means.
更多的血，更多的汗。
A lot more blood and a lot more sweat.
希望不是我们的人，老伙计。
Hopefully not any of ours, old boy.
我觉得没有你我们做不到，比利。
I don't think we can do this without you, Billy.
好吧，如果你愿意，我愿意。
Well, I'm up for it if you are.
我想我们需要你的拖船。
I think we're gonna need your tug.
我和海茜会沿着港口散步干掉所有还在巡逻的士兵。
Haysey and I will take a stroll along the harbor and take out any soldiers still patrolling.
弗雷迪会把他的小艇开过来，照顾s艇。
Freddy will bring his dinghy around and take care of the S-boats.
我们在拖船那儿等你。
We'll meet you by the tug boats.
公爵夫人呢?
And the Duchessa?
这就是苹果和我。
That's Apple and me.
我们会处理所有船员，然后炸掉锚。
We'll take care of any crew and blow the anchor.
摧毁他们的通讯。
And destroy their comms.
不知道你在船上会遇到什么。
Not sure what you'll meet on board.
带上我的老大和两个手下。
Take my top boy and two more of my men.
先生们，准备吧。
Gentlemen, let's prepare.
鈾?哦，鲨鱼，宝贝鈾?有这样的牙齿吗，亲爱的鈾?他给他们看珍珠白鈾?只是一把千斤顶刀鈾?老麦克希斯有吗，亲爱的鈾?他把它藏起来鈾?你知道鲨鱼什么时候咬人
鈾?Oh, the shark, babe 鈾? Has such teeth, dear 鈾? And he shows them pearly white 鈾? Just a jack-knife 鈾? Has old MacHeath, dear 鈾?And he keeps it out of sight 鈾?You know when that shark bites
鈾?用他的牙齿，亲爱的鈾?猩红的波涛开始蔓延鈾?漂亮的手套，哦，老麦克希斯戴着，亲爱的鈾?所以从来没有红色的痕迹鈾?在人行道上
鈾?With his teeth, dear 鈾? Scarlet billows starts to spread 鈾? Fancy gloves, oh, wears old MacHeath, dear 鈾?So there's never, never a trace of red 鈾?On the sidewalk
鈾?星期天早上，你不知道鈾吗?谎言的身体鈾?渗出生命鈾?有人在拐角处偷偷摸摸鈾?会是老刀子麦克吗?
鈾?On Sunday morning, don't you know 鈾? Lies a body 鈾? Oozing life 鈾? And someone sneakin' around the corner 鈾?Could that be old Mack the Knife?
鈾?有一艘拖船鈾?在河边，你不知道吗
鈾?There's a tug boat 鈾? Down by the river, don't cha know
鈾?一个水泥袋耷拉下来…
鈾?Where a cement bag's just a-drooping on down...
还没有。
Not yet.
我的先生。
Mein Herr.
Haysey……
Haysey...
就在左边，先生。
Up there on the left, sir.
是的。
Yes.
他撞车了!
He made a crash!
我们可以开那辆车，先生，省点皮鞋。
We could take that car, sir. Save us some shoe leather.
鈾?当心，老麦基回来了鈾?/我
鈾?Look out, old Macky is back 鈾?/i
传入的。
Incoming.
论文请。
Papers please.
——指挥官。-没事吧，弗雷迪?
- Commander. - All good, Freddy?
我们一出港就会启动炸药，长官。
Charges are set to go once we're out of the harbor, sir.
那我们继续吧。
Let's carry on then.
你喜欢你的礼物吗?
Did you enjoy your gift?
嗯。
Mmm.
我想现在是时候让狐狸向雌狐展示他的巢穴了。
I think now it's time that the fox shows his den to the vixen.
苍鹭，灯怎么还亮着?
Heron, why are the lights still on?
我用油灯照亮了房间，这样他们就不会注意到停电了。
I lit the room with oil lamps, so they wouldn't notice when the power went out.
-小心!
- Look out!
弗莱迪，装好88号，然后和海茜一起上第一艘拖船。
Freddy, rig this 88, then take the first tug with Haysey.
-晚安。- Guten abend。
- Gute nacht. - Guten abend.
晚上好。
Guten abend.
非常抱歉，老伙计。
Terribly sorry, old boy.
-你介意吗?我似乎……-…我把刀放错了地方。
- Do you mind? I seem to... - ...have misplaced my knife.
——同性恋者!
- Bugger!
谢谢你，比利。
Thank you, Billy.
——哦!
- Oh!
我希望那不是你的血，拉森。
I hope that's not your blood, Lassen.
我也希望如此。
I hope so too.
好了，伙计们，开船吧。
Okay, boys, cast off.
我们把这艘船弄出去吧。
Let's get this ship out of here.
继续。继续……去吧!
Go on. Go on... Go on!
还有三间这样的房间。
There's three more rooms just like this one.
这应该能在接下来的六个月里阻止德国潜艇的行动。
That should stop the U-boats for the next six months.
我们把这东西拖走吧。
Let's get this thing towed out of here.
我们来了，孩子们。
We are here, boys.
安静的。让我们设置一个警告。
Quietly. Let's set a warning.
我要你去船头把火神号绑在公爵夫人号上，拉森和我去舰桥。
I need you to go to the front of the boat and attach the Vulcan to the Duchessa, Lassen and I will head to the bridge.
好吧。
Okay.
站在右边。
Take the right side.
而你，站上去，把它启动。
And you, get up there and get this thing started.
格斯。
It's Gus.
所有人都就位了。
Everyone's in place.
怎么，你不会真觉得这能行吧?
What, you didn't actually think it would work, did you?
这是你的计划。
It was your plan.
好吧，让我们确保遵守我们的承诺。
Well, let's make sure we keep our end of the bargain.
回个信号，我就离开。
Signal back and I'll heave off.
那么，现在发生了什么?
So, what happens now?
我们等锚链爆炸。
We wait for the anchor chain to blow.
我们预计什么时候会发生?
When do we expect that to happen?
-我希望很快。
- Shortly, I hope.
然后我们就可以带走她了。
And then we're free to take her.
然而，真正的竞赛在燃料库耗尽后才开始。
However, the real race begins once the fuel depot goes.
那岛上所有的士兵都会出动。
Then we'll have every soldier on the island turning up.
我们可不想目睹这一切。
We don't wanna be around to witness that.
你绑在锚链上的保险丝有多长?
How long was that fuse you attached to the anchor chain?
我们很快就会知道了。
We'll find out soon enough.
等一下，你会抓住绳子的。
Wait for it, you're gonna catch the rope.
来吧。
Come on.
第一张多米诺骨牌倒下了。
First domino falls.
-挂上另一条线。-是的，老板。
- Hitch up the other line. - Yes, boss.
收拾残局。
Pick up the slack.
他们得在燃料堆爆炸前转移她。
They need to move her before the fuel dump blows.
赫伦，我们需要玛乔丽。
Heron, we need Marjorie.
把玛乔丽交给我吧。
Leave Marjorie to me.
我们会赶上你的。
We'll catch you up.
很好。
Very good.
我们走吧!
Let's go!
我不得不说，小姐
I have to say, Fraulein,
你表现得很好。
you were good.
你很狡猾。
And you were sly.
像狐狸一样狡猾的人只有两种。
There are only two types of people that are as sly as the fox.
德国人和犹太人。
The German and the Jew.
你也不是德国人。
And you are not German.
我想现在是时候……
I think now it's time...
-…为了一个真正的派对。
- ...for a real party.
这是不应该发生的。
That wasn't supposed to happen yet.
卸扣她!
Shackle her!
跟我来。
And follow me.
港口被攻击了!
The harbor is under attack!
他们的到来。
They're coming.
我们需要给引擎提供动力。
We need power on the engine.
-她太重了!-振作起来!
- She's too heavy! - Pick up the slack!
等待……
Wait...
她没动!
She's not moving!
火!火!火!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
等一下。
Wait for it.
我们需要增加引擎的动力。
We need more power on the engine.
给我更多的力量!更多的力量!
Give me more power! More power!
就是这样，它起作用了!
That's it, it's working!
-就是这样!
- That's it!
准备好了!
Ready!
——Haysey !
-  Haysey!
我们已经超出射程了。
We're out of range now.
-我不是专家。
- I'm no expert.
但你肩膀上有个大洞，海赛。
But you've got a big old hole in your shoulder, Haysey.
上尉，你能跟我解释一下这是怎么回事吗?
Captain, would you explain to me what's going on here?
没电了。
The power is gone.
燃料库遭到破坏。
The fuel depot has been sabotaged.
没人知道发生了什么。
And no one knows what's happening.
但这是你的错。
But this is your fault.
我的船在哪里?
Where is my ship?
公爵夫人，它去哪儿了?
The Duchessa, where did it go?
有人趁你不注意把他带走了。
Someone's taken him while you weren't looking.
你这个笨蛋!
You idiot!
你总是在不合适的时候说错话。
You always have to say something at the very wrong time.
和你在一起永远没有合适的时间!
There is never a right time with you!
你的贪婪和堕落让你无法履行职责。
Your greed and perversion has distracted you from your duties.
现在我的港口被毁了。
Now my harbor is destroyed.
我的船不见了!
And my ship is gone!
现在你也走了。谢谢你！
And now you're gone too. Thank you.
让人印象深刻。
Impressive.
听起来你的雷管起作用了。
Sounds like your detonators worked.
帽子,小姐。
Chapeau, mademoiselle.
你打得很好。你真是个狐狸精。
You play well. You really are the vixen.
我是吗?
Am I?
好吧，我的手露出来了。
Well, my hand's been revealed.
那么，现在怎么办?
So, what now?
现在我握着你的手，因为你对我所做的一切，我要加倍惩罚你。
Now, I possess your hand and for everything you have done to me, I will visit a thousand fold upon you.
是的。
Yeah.
但是没有。
But no.
-躺下。
- Lie down.
格斯，我们不能再等了。
Gus, we can't wait much longer.
他们的到来。
They're coming.
如果我们呆在这里，就会和其他人失去联系。
If we stay here, we'll lose contact with the others.
坚持住，比利。
Hold fast, Billy.
赫伦有自己的生存之道，而玛乔丽…祝你好运。
Heron has a way of surviving and Marjorie, well... good luck with that.
那是一艘巡逻艇向我们驶来。
That's a patrol boat coming towards us.
-古斯，我们得走了。现在。
- Gus, we need to leave. Now.
坚持……
Hold on...
这是他们。
It's them.
RH。
RH.
- - - - - - KB。马乔里。
- KB. -Marjorie.
同时穿得太正式和太不正式。
Overdressed and underdressed at the same time.
来吧，让我把你的镣铐解开。
Come on, let's get you out of those shackles.
进来，维奥莱特。
Come in, Violet.
呼叫维奥莱特号。
Calling H.M.S. Violet.
进来，维奥莱特。
Come in, Violet.
这是伴娘荣誉。
This is Maid Honor.
说吧，荣誉女仆。
Go ahead, Maid Honor.
——扬声器。
- Loudspeaker.
很抱歉在晚上这个时候打扰您，但我们发现有一两件商品您可能会感兴趣。
Sorry to bother you at this time of the night, but we've found ourselves with one or two items that might be of interest to you.
我们会合交接好吗?
Shall we rendezvous for a handover?
给我接庞德上将。
Get me Admiral Pound.
——是吗?先生-有好消息也有坏消息。-是的，是的。开始吧。
- Yes? Sir, - good news and bad news. - Yes, yes. Get to it.
坏消息是，他们没有击沉她。
Bad news, they didn't sink her.
好消息是，他们把她偷走了。
Good news, they stole her.
祝贺你，总理。
Congratulations, Prime Minister.
别动!
Hold it there!
指挥官。
Commander.
庞德上将命令你停止行动。
You were ordered by Admiral Pound to cease activities.
你没有。
You did not.
因此，你将被送回英格兰接受审判。你。
Therefore, you are to be returned to England to face a tribunal. You.
带着你的民兵回到你的拖船上。
Return to your tug with the rest of your militia.
-带他们去禁闭室-长官!
- Take them to the brig. -Sir!
我也很高兴见到你，指挥官。
Good to see you too, Commander.
单独的细胞。
Separate cells.
跟我来!
Follow me!
我们走吧!我们走吧!
Let's go! Let's get moving!
- RH。- - - - - - KB。
- RH. - KB.
来吧。
Come on.
继续，走吧。
Go on, move.
等一下，海员。
One moment, seaman.
比利。
Billy.
一只眼睛盯着边界……一只眼睛盯着酒吧。
One eye on the boundary... One eye on the pub.
总有一天他们会感谢你的。
They'll thank you for this one day.
我不确定那是不是我们真正想要的，是吧，殿下?
I'm not sure that's what we were really looking for, was it, Your Highness?
商店随时为你开门，少校。
Shop's open for you anytime, Major.
抱歉打扰了，首相，但我觉得你应该看看这个。
Sorry to intrude, Prime Minister, but M thought you should see this.
谢谢你，歌洛莉亚。
Thank you, Gloria.
流程。脸前!
-Line up. Face front!
排队。脸前!
Line up. Face front!
没必要大喊大叫。
No need to shout.
站着不动!
Stand still!
能给我一杯茶吗?
Any chance of a cup of tea?
你，退到墙边去。
You, back up to the wall.
脱布，飞蛾。
Off the cloth, moth.
站直!
Stand straight!
这个国家的高级陆军和海军指挥官从未如此团结一致地谴责。
Never before have the senior Military and Navy Commanders of this country been so united in their condemnation.
他们认为，我们的军队所依赖的纪律已经被那些不为主人服务的人破坏了，他们只对血腥、谋杀和伤害感兴趣。
It is their view that the discipline on which our armed forces depends has been undermined by men serving no master but their own thirst for blood, murder and mayhem.
那些不服从舰队司令直接命令的人，
Men who disobeyed a direct order from the Admiral of the fleet himself,
而是选择相信站在他身边的人的心血来潮和直觉。
and chose instead to trust the whim and intuition of the man standing beside him.
他们怎么敢。
How dare they.
就在今天早上，第一批美国士兵抵达英国土地，准备在欧洲与我们并肩作战。
When only this morning, the first American soldiers arrived on British soil, ready to stand shoulder to shoulder with us in Europe.
那些冒着生命危险穿越北大西洋的盟军，奇迹般地没有受到纳粹u型潜艇的干扰。
Allies who risked death crossing the North Atlantic, and only by some miracle found their crossing untroubled by Nazi U-boats.
我可以补充一句，这是一个令人高兴的情况，虽然无法解释，但它为美国参加欧洲战争扫清了道路。
A happy circumstance, I might add, which cannot be accounted for, but which has cleared the way for the United States to enter the European war.
我知道罗斯福总统对此感激不尽。
And for which I know President Roosevelt to be immeasurably grateful.
但是，撇开这一笔无法解释的好运不谈，对这群不服从命令的不守规矩的人该怎么办呢?
But setting aside this stroke of unexplained fortune, what is to be done with this unruly company who do not obey orders?
他们似乎已经形成了自己的非绅士战争部。
Who seem to have formed their own ministry of ungentlemanly warfare.
从现在开始，他们为我工作。
From now on, they work for me.